Guide to the Susan H. Douglas political Americana collection, [1783?]-1961.
Douglas, Susan H. Political Americana Collection, [1783?]-1961
- Series IX. Parades
  - Benjamin Harrison Portrait Head Walking Stick, ca. 1892; 2214.PD0074 (Box 118)
  - Item apparently not donated to Cornell University, 2214.PD0075 (Box -)
  - Garfield-Arthur Collapsible Paper Portrait Lantern, ca. 1880; 2214.PD0076 (Box 66)
  - Garfield-Arthur Collapsible Paper Portrait Lantern, ca. 1880; 2214.PD0077 (Box 66)
  - Grant "Union For Ever" Collapsible Paper Lantern, ca. 1868; 2214.PD0079 (Box 66)
  - Brass Torch Light mounted on Pole Handle, ca. 1856; 2214.PD0080 (Box 223)
  - Our Choice for President Woodrow Wilson Pennant, ca. 1912; 2214.PD0081 (Box 82)
  - Cylindrical Tin Torch Light, ca. 1884; 2214.PD0082 (Box 55)
  - Slotted Spherical Metal Torch Light, ca. 1860-1904; 2214.PD0083 (Box 64)
  - Small Cylindrical Tin Torch Light, ca. 1860-1904; 2214.PD0084 (Box 55)
  - Bucket-shaped Tin Torch Light, ca. 1860-1904; 2214.PD0085 (Box 56)
  - Hayes-Wheeler Pennant, ca. 1876; 2214.PD0086a (Box 153)
  - Missouri, New York, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia Flags, ca. 1876; 2214.PD0086b (Box 152)
  - Wooden Pen Holder used to Display Hayes-Wheeler Flags, 2214.PD0086c (Box 71)
  - Robert A. Taft Paper Garrison Cap and Button, ca. 1952; 2214.PD0087 (Box 139)
  - Eisenhower "Vet For Ike" Paper Garrison Cap, ca. 1948; 2214.PD0088 (Box 139)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Paper Garrison Cap, ca. 1952; 2214.PD0089 (Box 139)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Paper Garrison Cap, ca. 1952; 2214.PD0090 (Box 139)
  - Eisenhower "We Like Ike" Imitation Leather Belt, ca. 1952; 2214.PD0091 (Box 165)
  - Taylor-Fillmore Street Banner, ca. 1848; 2214.PD0092 (Box TBD)
  - Ward 5 Whig Association Washington Portrait Street Banner, ca. 1848; 2214.PD0093 (Box TBD)
  - Item apparently not donated to Cornell University, 2214.PD0095 (Box -)
  - Our Choice for President Theodore Roosevelt Pennant, ca. 1904-1912; 2214.PD0096 (Box 82)
  - "Votes For Women" Canvas Bag, ca. 1920; 2214.PD0097 (Box 150)
  - Cleveland-Stevenson Portrait Top Hat, 1892; 2214.PD0098 (Box 161)
  - Benjamin Harrison-Morton Portrait Top Hat, ca. 1888; 2214.PD0099 (Box TBD)
  - Eisenhower-Nixon "Crusade with Ike and Dick" Sun Hat, ca. 1952; 2214.PD0100 (Box 157)
  - Eisenhower "Official Campaign Hat" with Button, ca. 1952; 2214.PD0101 (Box 164)
  - Eisenhower "Ike" Civil War-style Forage Cap with Button, ca. 1952; 2214.PD0102 (Box 164)
  - Eisenhower "I Like 'Ike'" Beanie, ca. 1952; 2214.PD0103 (Box 164)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Baseball Cap, ca. 1952; 2214.PD0104 (Box 164)
  - McKinley-Hobart "Protection - Financial Stability - Reciprocity" Parade Banner, ca. 1896; 2214.PD0105 (Box TBD)
  - McKinley "Patriotism, Protection, Prosperity" Tin Horn, ca. 1896; 2214.PD0106 (Box 64)
  - Bryan Portrait Head Walking Stick, ca. 1896; 2214.PD0107 (Box 119)
  - Eisenhower "Ike" Dress and Belt, ca. 1956; 2214.PD0108 (Box 158)
  - Eisenhower Republican National Convention Pennant, 1956; 2214.PD0109 (Box 153)
  - Eisenhower Paper Sun Visor, 1956; 2214.PD0110 (Box 139)
  - Eisenhower "I Still Like Ike" Paper Sun Visor, ca. 1952-1956; 2214.PD0111 (Box 139)
  - Eisenhower "Ike" Parasol, ca. 1956; 2214.PD0112 (Box 158)
  - Stevenson-Kefauver Umbrella, ca. 1956; 2214.PD0113 (Box 153)
  - Eisenhower Republican Convention Delegate's Straw Hat, ca. 1952; 2214.PD0114 (Box 151)
  - Eisenhower Folding Cardboard Cap, ca. 1954-1956; 2214.PD0115 (Box 141)
  - Eisenhower-Nixon "We Like and We'll Stick With Ike and Dick" Paper Garrison Cap, 1956; 2214.PD0116 (Box 139)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Cone-Shaped Paper Hat, ca. 1956; 2214.PD0117 (Box 87)
  - Child's Plastic "I Like Ike" Hat with Moving Elephant, ca. 1956; 2214.PD0118 (Box 164)
  - Child's Plastic "I Like Ike" Hat with Moving Elephant, ca. 1956; 2214.PD0119 (Box 164)
  - "Junior Citizens for Eisenhower & Nixon" Paper Garrison Cap, 1956; 2214.PD0120 (Box 139)
  - Eisenhower Portrait "I Like Ike" Cap, ca. 1956; 2214.PD0121 (Box 164)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Paper Shopping Bag, ca. 1956; 2214.PD0122 (Box 87)
  - Stevenson-Kefauver "Adlai - Estes" Felt Hat, ca. 1956; 2214.PD0123 (Box 262)
  - Stevenson Democratic National Convention Cardboard Hat, 1956; 2214.PD0124 (Box 151)
  - "Hay! Krajewski!" Paper Garrison Cap, ca. 1956; 2214.PD0125 (Box 139)
  - McKinley "Protection / 1896" Portrait Head Walking Stick, 2214.PD0126 (Box 120)
  - Large Tubular Torch Light With Three Jets, ca. 1860-1904; 2214.PD0127a (Box 14)
  - Large Tubular Torch Light With Three Jets, ca. 1860-1904; 2214.PD0127b (Box 56)
  - Bucket-Shaped Torch Light, ca. 1860-1904; 2214.PD0127c (Box 56)
  - Kettle-shaped Iron Torch Light, ca. 1860-1904; 2214.PD0127d (Box 54)
  - Bryan Portrait Buggy Whip, ca. 1896; 2214.PD0128 (Box TBD)
  - McKinley-Roosevelt Tin "Dinner Pail" Candle Lantern, ca. 1900; 2214.PD0129 (Box 14)
  - Small Silver-Finish Torch Light for Mounting on Parade Helmet, ca. 1884; 2214.PD0130 (Box 64)
  - Cleveland-Thurman "He Is Dying in the Harness" Caricature Banner, ca. 1888; 2214.PD0131 (Box TBD)
- Series X Paper Miscellaneous
  Paper Miscellaneous: This category includes a wide variety of paper items intended to have a short use-life, including admission tickets, membership cards, post cards, fundraising letters and brochures, advertising cards, certificates, stationery, and stamps. Mrs. Douglas also included stereocard and cabinet photographs and some of the collection's bumper stickers in this category. Some of the items in this series (particularly post card sets) have been cataloged as groups rather than at the item level.
  - Nixon Standing Cutout Portrait, ca. 1960; 2214.PM0001 (Box 79)
  - Nixon Portrait Fan, ca. 1960; 2214.PM0003 (Box 79)
  - Meyner Paper Portrait Fan, 1957; 2214.PM0005 (Box 138)
  - Nixon Victory Stamps, ca. 1960; 2214.PM0006 (Box 79)
  - Nixon Portrait Stamps, ca. 1960; 2214.PM0007 (Box 79)
  - Dick-Pat Nixon Paper Shopping Bag, ca. 1960; 2214.PM0008 (Box 87)
  - Rockefeller Bumper Stickers, ca. 1960; 2214.PM0010 (Box 79)
  - Lodge for President 1960 Bumper Sticker, 2214.PM0012 (Box 79)
  - Nixon-Lodge Bumper Stickers, ca. 1960; 2214.PM0013 (Box 141)
  - McKinley Stereographs, ca. 1897-1900; 2214.PM0014 (Box 79)
  - Imitation Flower, 2214.PM0015 (Box 79)
  - "Do It With Dewey" Feather, ca. 1944-1948; 2214.PM0016 (Box 79)
  - "Republicans and Democrats are Very Much Alike" Paper Napkins, ca. 1952-1956; 2214.PM0017 (Box 79)
  - Eisenhower-Nixon "G.O.P." Paper Napkin, ca. 1952-1956; 2214.PM0018 (Box 79)
  - "President Eisenhower's Old Fashioned Beef Stew" Recipe Paper Napkin, ca. 1953-1961; 2214.PM0019 (Box 79)
  - Your Choice for President of the U.S. Questionnaire, ca. 1948; 2214.PM0020 (Box 79)
  - Presidential Poll Postcard, ca. 1932; 2214.PM0021 (Box 79)
  - "Ever-Shrinking Donkey Dollar", ca. 1944; 2214.PM0022 (Box 79)
  - "Returned, No Funds" Imitation Bank Check, ca. 1928; 2214.PM0023 (Box 79)
  - "Famous Army Officers" Portrait Envelope, 2214.PM0024 (Box 79)
  - Winfield Scott Embossed Stationery Fragment, 2214.PM0025 (Box 79)
  - Franklin, Delano, and Roosevelt Cartoon and Postmarked Envelope, ca. 1933; 2214.PM0026 (Box 79)
  - Bob Taft: Leader, Not Boss!!, ca. 1948; 2214.PM0027 (Box 79)
  - Our First President / Our Next President, ca. 1944-1952; 2214.PM0028 (Box 79)
  - Grant Memorial Number, ca. 1885; 2214.PM0029 (Box 79)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt Portrait Postage Stamps, ca. 1945; 2214.PM0030 (Box 79)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt-Garner Campaign Stamp, ca. 1932-1936; 2214.PM0031 (Box 79)
  - Willkie Campaign Stamps, ca. 1940; 2214.PM0032 (Box 79)
  - "Eisenhower For President: Our Stamp of Approval" Stamps, ca. 1952-1956; 2214.PM0033 (Box 79)
  - Eisenhower "Win With Ike / I Like Ike" Campaign Button Inserts, ca. 1952-1956; 2214.PM0034 (Box 79)
  - "We Want Ike!" Portrait Stamps, ca. 1952-1956; 2214.PM0035 (Box 79)
  - Republican Miniature Billboard Stamps, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0036 (Box 79)
  - "Nixon Now" Portrait Stamps, ca. 1960; 2214.PM0037 (Box 79)
  - Republican Participation Certificates and Envelope, 1936; 2214.PM0038 (Box 79)
  - United Republican Finance Committee Participation Certificate, 1940; 2214.PM0039 (Box 79)
  - New Jersey Republican Campaign Contribution Letter and Reciept, 1952; 2214.PM0040 (Box 79)
  - Republican Campaign Contribution Form, 1956; 2214.PM0041 (Box 79)
  - Stevenson-Kefauver "TV for Victory Fund" Campaign Contribution Items, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0042 (Box 79)
  - Republican Campaign Contribution Form, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0043 (Box 79)
  - Essex County Republican Finance Committee Pledge Card, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0044 (Box 79)
  - Assorted Newspaper and Magazine Clippings, ca. 1950-1950; 2214.PM0045 (Box 79)
  - Admission Tickets to the Impeachment of Andrew Johnson, 1868; 2214.PM0046 (Box 79)
  - 1872 National Democratic Convention Admission Ticket, 2214.PM0047 (Box 79)
  - Grand Army of the Republic Event Admission Ticket, 1879; 2214.PM0048 (Box 79)
  - 1888 Republican National Convention Admission Tickets, 2214.PM0049 (Box 79)
  - 1892 Republican National Convention Admission Ticket, 2214.PM0050 (Box 79)
  - Rip Van Winkle Club Membership Card, 1952; 2214.PM0051 (Box 79)
  - Railroad Press Lounge Admission Card, 1952; 2214.PM0052 (Box 79)
  - 1896 Republican National Convention Admission Tickets and Envelope, ca. 1896; 2214.PM0053 (Box 79)
  - Republican National Convention Admission Ticket, 1900; 2214.PM0054 (Box 79)
  - Democratic National Convention Admission Ticket, 1904; 2214.PM0055 (Box 79)
  - Republican National Convention Admission Ticket, 1908; 2214.PM0056 (Box 79)
  - Democratic National Convention Admission Tickets, 1912; 2214.PM0057 (Box 79)
  - Democratic National Convention Admission Ticket, 1924; 2214.PM0058 (Box 79)
  - Democratic National Convention Admission Tickets, 1936; 2214.PM0059 (Box 79)
  - Republican National Convention Admission Tickets, 1952; 2214.PM0060 (Box 79)
  - Democratic National Convention Admission Tickets, 1952; 2214.PM0061 (Box 79)
  - Taft-For-President Television Party Admission Ticket, ca. 1948; 2214.PM0062 (Box 79)
  - Eisenhower "We Like Ike" Ticket Stub, 1952; 2214.PM0063 (Box 79)
  - Eisenhower-Nixon Inaugural Items, 1953; 2214.PM0064 (Box 79)
  - Inaugural Ball Return Check, ca. 1953; 2214.PM0065 (Box 79)
  - Democratic National Convention Admission Tickets, 1956; 2214.PM0066 (Box 79)
  - "Ike Bandwagon" Rally Admission Ticket, 1956; 2214.PM0067 (Box 79)
  - Eisenhower Rally Admission Tickets, 1956; 2214.PM0068 (Box 79)
  - Tilden-Grant Novelty Advertising Cards, ca. 1876; 2214.PM0069 (Box 79)
  - Dwight Company Centennial Advertising Certificate, 1876; 2214.PM0070 (Box TBD)
  - "Political Information for 1880" Advertising Cards, ca. 1880; 2214.PM0071 (Box 79)
  - Arthur Portrait Advertising Card, ca. 1880; 2214.PM0072 (Box 79)
  - "1884 Patented Campaign Banner" Advertising Card, ca. 1883; 2214.PM0073 (Box 79)
  - "The Great Presidential Puzzle", ca. 1884; 2214.PM0074 (Box 79)
  - Cleveland-Blaine Portrait Advertising Card, 1884; 2214.PM0075 (Box 79)
  - Blaine-Cleveland Novelty Advertising Card, ca. 1884; 2214.PM0076 (Box 79)
  - Blaine Portrait Advertising Card, ca. 1884; 2214.PM0077 (Box 79)
  - Blaine Portrait Advertising Card, ca. 1884; 2214.PM0078 (Box 79)
  - Grover and Frances Folsom Cleveland Portrait Advertising Card, ca. 1886-1897; 2214.PM0079 (Box 79)
  - Cleveland Portrait Advertising Handbill, ca. 1891-1897; 2214.PM0080 (Box 80)
  - Grover and Frances Folsom Cleveland Portrait Advertising Card, ca. 1886-1897; 2214.PM0081 (Box 80)
  - Cleveland-Thurman Portrait Advertising Card, ca. 1888; 2214.PM0082 (Box 80)
  - Cleveland-Benjamin Harrison-Morton-Thurman Portrait Advertising Card, ca. 1888; 2214.PM0083 (Box 80)
  - Cleveland-Thurman Advertising Flier, 1888; 2214.PM0084 (Box 80)
  - Thurman Portrait Advertising Card, ca. 1888; 2214.PM0085 (Box 80)
  - Cleveland Portrait Advertising Card, 1888; 2214.PM0086 (Box 80)
  - Cleveland and Benjamin Harrison Portrait Advertising Cards, ca. 1888-1892; 2214.PM0087 (Box 80)
  - "Presidential Possibilities" Advertising Card Set, ca. 1892; 2214.PM0088 (Box 80)
  - Cleveland Portrait Advertising Card, ca. 1892; 2214.PM0089 (Box 80)
  - Presidential Portrait Advertising Cards, ca. 1888; 2214.PM0090 (Box 80)
  - William and Ida Saxton McKinley Portrait Knife Advertisement Clipping, ca. 1897; 2214.PM0091 (Box 80)
  - McKinley Portrait Advertising Handbill, ca. 1897-1901; 2214.PM0092 (Box 80)
  - The "Lincoln Car", 1898; 2214.PM0093 (Box 80)
  - "The White House and Its Next Occupant" Advertising Card, ca. 1904; 2214.PM0094 (Box 80)
  - The Electoral Vote of, 1908; 2214.PM0095 (Box 80)
  - Bryan-William H. Taft Portrait Advertising Card, ca. 1908; 2214.PM0096 (Box 80)
  - William H. Taft Speaks to the American Public through the Victor, ca. 1908; 2214.PM0097 (Box 80)
  - "Which Bill?" Portrait Advertising Card, ca. 1908; 2214.PM0098 (Box 80)
  - William H. Taft-Sherman Portrait Blotting Paper Samples, ca. 1908-1912; 2214.PM0099 (Box 80)
  - Harding Portrait Advertising Leaflet, ca. 1920-1923; 2214.PM0100 (Box 80)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt Portrait Advertising Handbill, ca. 1933-1934; 2214.PM0101 (Box 80)
  - Harriman Portrait Eyeglass Tissue Samples, ca. 1952-1956; 2214.PM0102 (Box 80)
  - Eisenhower-Nixon Inaugural Ball Souvenir, 1953; 2214.PM0103 (Box 80)
  - 1956 Election Gadget, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0104 (Box 80)
  - Eisenhower Portrait Advertising Handbill, 1956; 2214.PM0105 (Box 80)
  - Marks' Adjustable Folding Chair Advertising Card, 2214.PM0106 (Box 80)
  - Democratic National Convention Tablet Sugar Wrappers, 2214.PM0107 (Box 80)
  - "For Salt River...Direct Through Without Landing" Newspaper Clipping, ca. 1856; 2214.PM0108 (Box 80)
  - Anti-McClellan Cartoon, ca. 1864; 2214.PM0109 (Box 80)
  - The Last Ditch Of the Chivalry, or a President in Petticoats, ca. 1865; 2214.PM0110 (Box 80)
  - McClellan Portrait Stationery Item, ca. 1861; 2214.PM0111 (Box 80)
  - Grant In Peace, ca. 1868; 2214.PM0112 (Box 80)
  - Presidents Of U.S., ca. 1868-1877; 2214.PM0113 (Box 80)
  - Republican Party Handbill, ca. 1880; 2214.PM0114 (Box 80)
  - Cleveland Portrait Card, ca. 1885-1897; 2214.PM0115 (Box 80)
  - Prohibition Party Campaign Card, ca. 1904; 2214.PM0116 (Box 80)
  - William H. Taft-Sherman Portrait Envelope, ca. 1908; 2214.PM0117 (Box 80)
  - William H. Taft "Welcome to Our President" Portrait Badge, ca. 1908-1913; 2214.PM0118 (Box 80)
  - Dayton Harding Boosters Parade Instructions and Hat Band Ornament, ca. 1920; 2214.PM0119 (Box 80)
  - Charles C. Deubel Portrait Card, 1948; 2214.PM0121 (Box 80)
  - It's Time For A Change!, ca. 1952; 2214.PM0122 (Box 80)
  - Republican Party Presidential Petition, 1952; 2214.PM0123 (Box 80)
  - East Orange Independent Citizens For Eisenhower Letter, ca. 1952; 2214.PM0124 (Box 80)
  - "Look What They Did To Your Income!" Handbill, ca. 1952; 2214.PM0125 (Box 80)
  - "Vote Republican" Bookmark, ca. 1952; 2214.PM0126 (Box 80)
  - "A Democrat Speaks" Handbill, ca. 1952; 2214.PM0127 (Box 80)
  - Robert A. Taft Elephant Pin and Display Card, ca. 1948-1952; 2214.PM0128 (Box 80)
  - Eisenhower-Nixon-Smith Handbill, ca. 1952; 2214.PM0129 (Box 80)
  - "Harry Knows / Harry Says / Harriman Will Win!" Handbill, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0130 (Box 80)
  - "Honesty is No Substitute for Experience" Satirical Card, ca. 1952; 2214.PM0131 (Box 80)
  - "I Like Ike / But I'm Gonna' Vote for Stevenson" Handbill, ca. 1952-1956; 2214.PM0132 (Box 80)
  - "Don't let this happen to You! Vote for Ike!" Cards, ca. 1952-1956; 2214.PM0133 (Box 80)
  - "Eisenhower For President" Handbill, ca. 1952-1956; 2214.PM0134 (Box 80)
  - Eisenhower-Nixon Volunteer Card, ca. 1952-1956; 2214.PM0135 (Box 80)
  - Eisenhower-Nixon Promotional Cards, ca. 1952-1956; 2214.PM0136 (Box 80)
  - Here's Pat and Dick Nixon!, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0137 (Box 80)
  - Are You Tired of Peace and Prosperity?, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0138 (Box 80)
  - Pocket Reminder: Eisenhower Accomplishments, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0139 (Box 80)
  - Here's What Ike Put In Your Wallet!, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0140 (Box 80)
  - Thank You, Ike, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0141 (Box 80)
  - Who Does Ike Need in Congress?, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0142 (Box 80)
  - Eisenhower Speech Excerpt Card, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0143 (Box 80)
  - Vote The Republican Ticket Straight, 2214.PM0144 (Box 80)
  - New Jersey Republican Conference Worker Card, 2214.PM0145 (Box 80)
  - Lincoln Portrait Stationery Item, 2214.PM0146 (Box 80)
  - Design for a New Coin of the C. S. A., ca. 1861; 2214.PM0147 (Box 80)
  - Winfield Scott Portrait Stationery, ca. 1861; 2214.PM0148 (Box 80)
  - Stephen A. Douglas Portrait Stationery Item, ca. 1860-1861; 2214.PM0149 (Box 80)
  - A Distinguished Arrival, 1865; 2214.PM0150 (Box 80)
  - Radical Love For The Soldier, ca. 1866; 2214.PM0151 (Box 80)
  - Grover Cleveland Portrait, ca. 1882; 2214.PM0152 (Box 80)
  - Abraham Lincoln Portrait, 2214.PM0153 (Box 80)
  - Hobart Portrait Cabinet Photograph, ca. 1896; 2214.PM0154 (Box 80)
  - McKinley Portrait Cabinet Photograph, ca. 1896-1901; 2214.PM0155 (Box 80)
  - Woodrow Wilson Portrait, 2214.PM0156 (Box 80)
  - Harry S. Truman Portrait, ca. 1945-1953; 2214.PM0157 (Box 80)
  - The Highest Recommendation, ca. 1948; 2214.PM0158 (Box 80)
  - The Ticket for You - Not Just the Few, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0159 (Box 80)
  - Harold Stassen Portrait, 2214.PM0160 (Box 81)
  - Abraham Lincoln and Mary Todd Lincoln Photographic Portraits, 2214.PM0161 (Box 81)
  - Hon. Grover Cleveland, 2214.PM0162 (Box 81)
  - "Carry On With Hoover" Sticker, ca. 1928-1932; 2214.PM0163 (Box 81)
  - Landon-Knox Stickers, ca. 1936; 2214.PM0164 (Box 81)
  - Willkie Stickers, ca. 1940; 2214.PM0165 (Box 81)
  - "Work withWallace" Sticker, ca. 1948; 2214.PM0166 (Box 81)
  - "William O. Douglas For President" Sticker, ca. 1948; 2214.PM0167 (Box 81)
  - Dewey-Warren "All 48 in '48" Sticker, 1948; 2214.PM0168 (Box 81)
  - Robert A. Taft Sticker, ca. 1952; 2214.PM0169 (Box 81)
  - "Stevenson For President" Stickers, ca. 1952-1956; 2214.PM0170 (Box 81)
  - Republican Calendar Sticker, ca. 1955-1956; 2214.PM0171 (Box 81)
  - Eisenhower-Nixon Bumper Stickers, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0172 (Box 81)
  - "Stassen for President" Sticker, 2214.PM0173 (Box 81)
  - Democratic Women's Day Sticker, 2214.PM0174 (Box 81)
  - Theodore Roosevelt Postcards, ca. 1896-1916; 2214.PM0175 (Box 81)
  - McKinley Memorial Postcards, ca. 1901; 2214.PM0176 (Box 81)
  - Alice Roosevelt-Nicholas Longworth Postcard, 1904; 2214.PM0177 (Box 81)
  - Theodore Roosevelt-Fairbanks Postcard, 1904; 2214.PM0178 (Box 81)
  - Dee-Lighted, ca. 1906; 2214.PM0179 (Box 81)
  - Theodore Roosevelt-White House "Puzzle Postcard", ca. 1906-1908; 2214.PM0180 (Box TBD)
  - Oh! Look Who's Here!, 1907; 2214.PM0181 (Box 81)
  - Bear Puzzle Postcard Set, 1907; 2214.PM0182 (Box 81)
  - "What Are The Wild Waves Saying" Postcard, 1907; 2214.PM0183 (Box 81)
  - Bryan-Kern Portrait Postcards, ca. 1908; 2214.PM0184 (Box 81)
  - William H. Taft-Sherman Portrait Postcards, ca. 1908-1912; 2214.PM0185 (Box 81)
  - McKinley-Theodore Roosevelt-William H. Taft Postcard, 1908; 2214.PM0186 (Box 81)
  - Bryan-Kern Postcards, ca. 1908; 2214.PM0187 (Box 81)
  - The Washington-Bryan Combination Picture, 1908; 2214.PM0188a (Box 81)
  - The Washington-Bryan Combination Picture, 1908; 2214.PM0188b (Box 81)
  - William H. Taft Photographic Postcards, ca. 1911; 2214.PM0189 (Box 81)
  - Theodore Roosevelt Postcards, ca. 1912; 2214.PM0190 (Box 81)
  - William H. Taft Postcards, ca. 1912; 2214.PM0191 (Box 81)
  - Wilson Postcards, ca. 1912; 2214.PM0192 (Box 81)
  - Theodore Roosevelt-Hiram Johnson Washington Party Postcard, ca. 1912; 2214.PM0193 (Box 81)
  - Wilson Portrait Postcards, ca. 1912-1916; 2214.PM0194 (Box 81)
  - Coolidge-Cox Postcard, ca. 1919; 2214.PM0195 (Box 81)
  - The President and Mrs. Warren G. Harding, ca. 1921-1924; 2214.PM0196 (Box 81)
  - "Sure - I'm for Roosevelt" Postcard, ca. 1940; 2214.PM0197 (Box 81)
  - Anti-Truman Postcard, ca. 1945-1953; 2214.PM0198 (Box 81)
  - The Way Ahead: Dewey-Warren, ca. 1948; 2214.PM0199 (Box 81)
  - Henry A. Wallace Portrait Postcard, ca. 1948; 2214.PM0200 (Box 81)
  - Thurmond-Wright "States' Rights Democrats" Postcard, ca. 1948; 2214.PM0201 (Box 81)
  - Nixon Family Portrait Postcard, 1952; 2214.PM0202 (Box 81)
  - Truman-Eisenhower Cartoon Postcard, ca. 1952; 2214.PM0203 (Box 81)
  - Eisenhower Postcards, ca. 1952-1956; 2214.PM0204 (Box 81)
  - Eisenhower-Prescott Bush Postcard, ca. 1953-1961; 2214.PM0205 (Box 81)
  - Eisenhower Family Portrait Postcards, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0206 (Box 81)
  - Eisenhower-Nixon Postcard and Handbills, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0207 (Box 81)
  - Republican Party "G.O.P. '56" Postcards, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0208 (Box 81)
  - You Bet My Vote Counts!, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0209 (Box 81)
  - "What Don't You Like? ... peace or prosperity" Postcard, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0210 (Box 81)
  - Eisenhower Portrait Postcard and Handbills, ca. 1952-1956; 2214.PM0211 (Box 81)
  - "I am for Stassen for President" Reply Card, 2214.PM0212 (Box 81)
  - Eisenhower Campaign Event Invitation, ca. 1952; 2214.PM0213 (Box 81)
  - Eisenhower-Nixon Club Membership Cards, ca. 1952-1956; 2214.PM0214 (Box 81)
  - "I've Switched to ... Adlai" Bumper Sticker, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0215 (Box 138)
  - "Ike & Chris Will Not Miss" Bumper Sticker, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0216 (Box 141)
  - Andrews-Werdel "States Rights / Tax Relief" Bumper Sticker, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0217 (Box 141)
  - Krajewski "Say Hay!!" Bumper Sticker, ca. 1952-1956; 2214.PM0218 (Box 138)
  - "Adlai, Estes, and Joe Smith" Bumper Stickers, ca. 1956; 2214.PM0219 (Box TBD)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Portrait Armbands, ca. 1952; 2214.PM0220 (Box TBD)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Portrait Window Ornament, ca. 1952; 2214.PM0221 (Box TBD)
  - Theodore Roosevelt Cartoon Postcard, 1907; 2214.PM0222 (Box 81)
  - Henry Clay Portrait Clipping, 2214.PM0223 (Box 81)
- Series XI. Posters
  Posters: This series is primarily comprised of large political portrait images intended for public or home display.
  - Grover Cleveland. Democratic Candidate for President., ca. 1884; 2214.PO0001 (Box 84)
  - Theodore Roosevelt., 1904; 2214.PO0002 (Box 84)
  - Charles W. Fairbanks., 1904; 2214.PO0003 (Box 84)
  - Calvin Coolidge For President/ Charles G. Dawes For Vice-President, 1924; 2214.PO0004 (Box 84)
  - Calvin Coolidge: "We are the possessors...", 1921; 2214.PO0005 (Box 84)
  - We're Backing Bill Douglas, ca. 1948; 2214.PO0006 (Box 84)
  - Thomas E. Dewey, ca. 1948; 2214.PO0007 (Box 98)
  - Earl Warren, ca. 1948; 2214.PO0008 (Box 98)
  - Thomas E. Dewey/Unanimously Chosen ...Earl Warren/Governor ..., 1948; 2214.PO0009 (Box 84)
  - Thomas E. Dewey, ca. 1948; 2214.PO0010 (Box 95)
  - Earl Warren, ca. 1948; 2214.PO0011 (Box 95)
  - Win With Ike!, ca. 1952; 2214.PO0012 (Box 95)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower, 1952; 2214.PO0013 (Box 84)
  - Richard Nixon, 1952; 2214.PO0014 (Box 84)
  - America needs Eisenhower For a Durable Peace, 1952; 2214.PO0015 (Box 84)
  - America Needs Eisenhower, 1952; 2214.PO0016 (Box 84)
  - ...for all the people: Stevenson and Sparkman, 1952; 2214.PO0017 (Box 84)
  - America Needs A Winner, 1948; 2214.PO0018 (Box 84)
  - The Republican Party encourages every form of American industry!, ca. 1884; 2214.PO0019 (Box 84)
  - For President: Warren G. Harding, 1920; 2214.PO0020 (Box 85)
  - Republican Meeting: Hughes and Fairbanks Club of Doylestown, 1916; 2214.PO0021 (Box 85)
  - "Keep Him On The Job", 1932; 2214.PO0022 (Box 85)
  - William McKinley: Republican Candidate for President, 1896; 2214.PO0023 (Box 98)
  - Vote for Ike to-day, ca. 1952; 2214.PO0024 (Box 95)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower, ca. 1952; 2214.PO0025 (Box 95)
  - It's Up To You Now!, 1952; 2214.PO0026 (Box 85)
  - Victory and Reform: The Democratic Souvenir, 1884; 2214.PO0033 (Box 85)
  - For President: James G. Blaine, 1884; 2214.PO0034 (Box 85)